(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
私の色はあなたに見つけてもらえますか？
Can you find my color for me?
born to be real
どこまでも言えてたら
If only I could say everything
どこまでも笑えてたら
If only I could laugh all the way
見事も無くしたんだ
I've lost everything completely
自分に嘘ついて
Lying to myself
背伸びした一人前で
Pretending to be a grown-up
なりふり構わずなんて
Without caring about appearances
スカした表情に白けて
Wearied by a pretentious face
何を守れるの？
What can I protect?
永遠に愛したって
Even if I love you forever
期待したって違うでしょ
Even if I expect it, it's different, right?
見ていたい 誰にとっての天使だろ
I want to see whose angel I am
何も言わないで
Don't say anything
腐らないで 止まらないから
Don't rot, because I won't stop
渦巻く人にわき目も
Without even a glance at the swirling crowd
この声が届くはず
This voice should reach you
born to be real
生きていたい
I want to live
たったいま投げられた言葉
The words that were just thrown
その意味を壊すかもしれないなんて
To think they might break that meaning
たんねえな　言えばいい1人前で
It's not enough, just say it as a full-grown adult
手を振るか試すつもりで
Intending to test if I'll wave back
この正義の反対は別の正義じゃないんだ
The opposite of this justice isn't another justice
Every answer
わからないんだ
I don't know
誰か教えて
Someone tell me
永遠に愛したって期待したって違うでしょ
Even if I love forever, even if I expect, it's different, right?
一体何を以てこの答えだろ
Just what leads to this answer?
何も言えないよ　わかんないよ　だから歌うんだ
I can't say anything, I don't know, so I'll sing
胸が邪魔して君のために
My heart gets in the way, for you
この声が枯れるまで
Until this voice withers
唇は...
My lips...
生まれた理由なんて意味なんて
The reason for being born, the meaning
君のあとづけままで
Leaving them as your afterthoughts
だけど出会えたそれが全てなんだ
But having met you, that's everything
例え泣いたって笑ったって変わんない未来
Whether I cry or laugh, the future won't change
自分に今日も嘘ついて
Lying to myself again today
何をどうしたって腐ったって
No matter what I do, even if I rot
どうせ同じなら
If it's the same anyway
嘘つきはやめたんだ
I've stopped being a liar
永遠に愛したって期待したって違うでしょ
Even if I love forever, even if I expect, it's different, right?
一体誰を以てこの答えだろ
Just who leads to this answer?
何も言わないで腐らないで　もう止まらないから
Don't say anything, don't rot, because I won't stop anymore
大切な人にはきっと
To the precious person, surely
この声が届くはず
This voice should reach
唇は...
My lips...
born to be real
イエーイ！ということでみなさん、こんやっぴー！ホロライブ4期生、常闇トワ様です！
Yay! So everyone, konyappii! I'm Hololive 4th Gen, Tokoyami Towa-sama!
はい、ということで、この広いステージに今トワ1人。そして先ほど歌ったのは…
Yes, so, Towa's all alone on this wide stage. And what I just sang was...
3rdフェスぶりだね、born to be real、トワのオリジナル曲になります。
Since the 3rd Fes, "born to be real," it's my original song.
どうだったかな？
How was it?
ちょっと3rdフェスとはね、若干、若干違う振りにはなってましたけれども、何でかって言うと…
The choreo was slightly, slightly different from the 3rd Fes, but as for why...
日が空いているから！
Because some time has passed!
そう、まあそんなことは気にしない気にしない。
Right, well, don't worry about that, don't worry.
でも、このすいちゃんが好きなね、この振りは、この振りはみんな、どうだったかな？いいでしょ？
But what did everyone think of this choreo that Sui-chan likes? It's good, right?
はい、ということで、今日はね、あの常闇トワの誕生日なんです！
Yes, so today is Tokoyami Towa's birthday!
ハッピーバースデー・トゥー・ミー！
Happy Birthday to me!
はい、みんなハッピーバースデーありがとう。あ、はいコメントでもね、多分ね、多分って何だろうね。
Yes, thank you everyone for the happy birthday. Oh, and in the comments too, probably...
もう先読みで、あ、ありがとう！ハッピーバースデーありがとうね！
Already anticipating it, oh, thank you! Thank you for the happy birthday!
はい、先読み完了。ということで、はい、じゃあね今日のハッシュタグは…
Yes, anticipation complete. So, okay, today's hashtag is...
#常闇トワ聖誕祭2022 で呟いてください！
Please tweet with #TokoyamiTowaSeitansai2022!
ぜひぜひトレンドにも入りたいので、もういっぱい呟いてくんないと…
I really want to get into the trends, so if you don't tweet a lot...
怒っちゃうぞ！
I'll get angry!
はい、気持ち悪いということで。
Yes, that was gross.
はい、じゃあね、今日の配信は、なんと、なんと、いつもはね、トークしたりとかちょっとしながら歌ってライブをするんだけど…
So today's stream is, amazingly, usually I talk a bit while singing for the live, but...
今日は、もう歌をいっぱい歌いたいなと思っているので、トークは短め！
Today I want to sing lots of songs, so the talk will be short!
いっぱい歌うのでたくさん見てください！聞いてね！
I'll sing a lot, so please watch a lot! Listen, okay!
ちょっとこだわりもあるんでね、ちゃんと見ていっぱい聞いて見ていっぱい聞いていっぱい呟いてくれたら嬉しいな。
I've put a lot into this, so I'd be happy if you watched and listened carefully and tweeted a lot.
はい、では、この後は、トワの好きな曲をたくさんのゲストといっぱい歌いますので聞いてください！
Yes, so after this, I'll be singing songs I like with many guests, so please listen!
では、ゲストコーナーへどうぞ！ボーン！
Well then, on to the guest corner! Boom!
白銀の獅子は　駆けて　駆けて　駆け続けている
The silver lioness is running, running, keeps on running
もう不安に振り返ることはないから
Because there's no more looking back in anxiety
百獣の王は　九十九を信じるから王なんだ
The king of beasts is a king because she believes in the ninety-nine
Be hard, the pride, and that's the pride
それこそ私の誇り
That is precisely my pride
Lioness' Pride
作詞・作曲：かめりあ
Lyrics/Composition: Camellia
ここを独り抗って
Resisting here alone,
ずっと独りなんだろうって思ってた
I thought I'd be alone forever.
前だけ睨んで
Gazing only forward,
ただ命懸けて
simply risking my life,
足跡見失って
losing sight of my footsteps.
変わらないと
Knowing things won't change,
交わさないと
knowing we won't interact,
はぐれ山猫だって笑った
I laughed at being a stray wildcat.
音もなかった世界 満ちて広げてゆく
Filling and expanding a silent world.
人たちの声や生の目に 絆されて
Enchanted by the voices of people and their living eyes.
私は変わりつつ 蕾のライオンです
I am changing, a lion in the bud.
尖った爪を研ぐ 友の前歩くため
Sharpening my pointed claws to walk before my friends.
真っ白い獅子は 群れて群れて群れを抱く
The pure white lion herds and herds, embracing the pride.
それが私を支えてくれるから
Because that is what supports me.
誇れる場所を 謳え謳え 飢える者たち
Sing and sing of this place of pride, you hungry ones.
WE HAVE THE PRIDE IN
OR IS THE PRIDE
それこそは 私の誇り
That is my pride.
蹴ら 飼い殺して 縄張りの
Kicking... keeping them tamed within the territory,
線を 今日も無差別に引いてた
indiscriminately drawing lines today as well.
目指した物だけ 輝く物だけ
Only the things I aimed for, only the things that shine,
そして ただ 迷うだけ
and then, simply getting lost.
見失い軌道 噂の元を
Losing the trajectory, tracing the source of rumors,
導き出してる 築いたあの日
deriving it all since the day I realized.
溶けなかった 凍土にやがて広がりゆく
On the permafrost that wouldn't melt, it eventually spreads.
私たちの根っこ 少しずつ 肥えていくから
Our roots are gradually growing rich.
明日をずっと 今日離れていても
Even if we are far apart today or tomorrow,
寂しげに 向け微笑む 友に声届けるため
to deliver my voice to the friend who smiles lonely at me.
一輪の獅子は 咲いて咲いて 咲き誇りたいのさ
The single lion wants to bloom and bloom in full glory.
燃えいづ時は 見守る人のために
When it burns out, it's for those who watch over us.
百歌の王は 一緒に一緒に 咲き誇りたいのさ
The king of a hundred songs wants to bloom together in glory.
WE CAN BE THE KING OF BEASTS TOGETHER
白銀の獅子は 駆けて駆けて 駆け続けてる
The silver lion runs and runs, continuing to run.
どこを振り返ることはないから
Because there's nowhere to look back to.
百獣の王は 救世を信じ カラーを名乗るさ
The king of beasts believes in salvation and shows its colors.
今はまだ前だよ
We're still moving forward.
この夢だけを
With only this dream,
見て走っていられる
I can keep on running.
後ろに大切なわがたちの 群れの元があるから
Because behind us lies the foundation of our precious pride.
WE HAVE THE PRIDE IN
OR IS THE PRIDE
それこそは 私の誇り
That is my pride.
High Tide
作詞・作曲・編曲：ZSunder
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: ZSunder
When you look up at the night sky, what do you see?
The glowing beauty in the twilight, it's no mystery
Now watch me at the scene, I'll light it all up
When the time has come, I'll be rising high
Longing for me like a lifeline, whenever you see
my shine
I'll catch your eye
Ah...
Its pulling you in like gravity
You will be bowing on your knees yeah
Pulling you in close to me
Watch my glory and might
Following me like a high tide
My reign will never stop
The tide begins to rise up to the top
Let my power ignite
Following me like a high tide
I can be a bright enigma
It's no surprise
But you'll give in to the brilliance
Like a moth to a light
Playing hard to get but I ain't patient
You'll succumb to my blinding radiance yeah
When you look up at the night sky
What do you see?
My shine!
An effulgent sight
Its pulling you in like gravity
You will be bowing on your knees yeah
Pulling you in close to me
Watch my glory and might
Following me like a high tide
My reign will never stop
The tide begins to rise up to the top
Let my power ignite
Following me like a high tide
I shine the brightest in the night
The way the waves come high
Its pulling you in like gravity
You will be bowing on your knees yeah
Pulling you in close to me
Watch my glory and might
Following me like a high tide
My reign will never stop
The tide begins to rise up to the top
Let my power ignite
Following me like a high tide
mayday,mayday
作詞・作曲:Junky
Lyrics & Composition: Junky
Mayday, mayday
メーデー声は届いてる 心がズキッと痛いみたい
Mayday, can you hear my voice? My heart feels a sharp pain
平然なんて魅力的に見せるテクニックはすぐにクラクラ
The technique of looking so charmingly calm, I'm already dizzy
メーデーそれじゃ物足りない すぐにもっともっと欲張りな
Mayday, that's not enough, soon even more and more greedily
ヘイヘイもっと焦らしてよ あなたの心に入っていたいの
Hey hey, tease me more, I want to be in your heart
あぁ 見透いた甘い罠
Ah, a transparent sweet trap
あぁ はめてあげようか
Ah, shall I set it for you?
あぁ 自在にコントロールしていたはずなのに
Ah, I thought I was controlling it freely
クラクラしちゃうぞ 眩暈倍誘われ
Making me dizzy, the dizziness is doubled by the invitation
クラクラしちゃった あぁ もうお手上げ
I've become dizzy, ah, I give up now
逃げたいわけじゃなくてね クラクラが丁度いい
It's not that I want to run away, this dizziness is just right
なんて君の前じゃ絶対 ヘルプミーして
Saying that in front of you, definitely "Help me"
メーデー舵が取れないの 気持ちがモヤっと晴れないし
Mayday, I can't take the helm, my feelings are hazy and won't clear up
メーデー何か言いたいね 今どき身の程もちょうどもちょうどもちょうど
Mayday, I want to say something, nowadays my status is also just right
絶対あるわけないじゃない 絶対にただの勘違い
There's no way it's true, it's definitely just a misunderstanding
場外蹴散らすヒラのワザ 踊らされているこの感じ
Outside the ring, a commoner's skill, this feeling of being danced around
とっても溶け出すような体温に満たされ
Being filled with a body temperature that seems to melt away
願ったアタシじゃないダイタイ ホーレスミー
The me I didn't wish for, mostly "Bless me"
mayday,mayday
だってもう絶対プライドにあって
Because I'm already certainly in my pride
私を困らせて
Troubling me
なんとも私笑わせたい
Somehow I want to make you laugh
絶対
Absolutely
レスミーして
Rescue me
ねえ、どうして
Hey, why
愛はいたずらするんだろう
Does love play tricks on us?
ねえ、傷は
Hey, as for the wounds
細かい痛みも消えるな
Don't let even the smallest pains disappear
本来は案外簡単に
Normally, unexpectedly easily
否定して壊れちゃうけど
It's denied and broken, but
気がつけば手を伸ばしちゃって
Before I knew it, I reached out my hand
その体苦しくて
That body is painful
君も手を伸ばしてくれ　ほら
You reach out your hand too, look
痛い　ここにいたいのがマイ
It hurts, I want to stay here, it's my...
落ち着く場所　その手で触れてよ
Calming place, touch it with those hands
ほらメイデイ
Look, Mayday
クラクラしちゃいそうな愛を　誘われ
Invited by a love that makes me dizzy
フラフラになっちゃわ　もう
I'm becoming lightheaded already
Help me!
Rescue me!
Save me!
Mayday!
だってもう　駆け出すような愛を
Because already, a love that feels like running out
嫌まわり　吐きだそう
Venting out the unpleasantness
溢れ出したんだ
It started to overflow
もうレスミーして
Rescue me already
ALICE&u
All my eyes deceive with me, your soul starts to fade
Unleash your magic to me
Now it's time not to worry to be in between me
A journey we have to see
Lurida rarira incomplete melody
Sung with a sweet but yet so sad symphony
Our bounds and feelings start to flow to me
I can't find a way when you're not even here
Always me
Let all the words I could say to you right now
I can't believe that you are the one for me
Would you come with me to the darkness
It's a kiss that never ever ever with everything
Let the time send this song to your ears, I hope
And we will sing it to the most of melody
The magic that we've lost
Every day I would pray my heart reached as far
Even type of worry in the light I could see
Do you want me to be here?
Knowing all the emotions you're supposed to feel
Even voice I want to hear
Shalala shalira incomplete melody
I'll be in your ears is destiny
Lurida rarira incomplete memory
Showing all the realm that I have ever feel
Yooh-mmm-there-sing it!
Shalala!
夜の曲
Night song
Shalala!
声よ燃える
My voice, burn
マジック紡ぐの欠片たちは
The fragments of the magic we've spun
今光になる
Are becoming light now
新たな喜びを
A new joy...
歌おう
Let's sing
Lurida rarira incomplete melody...
legacy
Let the wind, let the sea carry this melody
Timeless song that carry all the wish
I believe
All the words I could say right now,
I can only tell you a little bit
Overwhelmingly too captivated to ever be able
to leave with every scene
Let the time send this sound to you,
I hope that you will sing it to me
Lost of the melodies that I tried to love
Everyday I will sing it aloud and I will try to shine
この声を聴いて
Listen to this voice
足りない歌詞を足そう
Let's add the missing lyrics
Apa arti yang telah kuterima
What is the meaning I have received
Hati yang telah kupendam
The heart I have kept inside
A gentle breeze pass to your soul this time
Everything will be fine
Everyday I will sing it aloud
this is my time to shine
常闇の闇に囚われたまま
Trapped in the darkness of the eternal night
奏でる悲鳴を
The screams I play
聞かせて
Let me hear them
さぁ 爪を研いだら
Now, once you've sharpened your claws
まだ子供のようなあなたのために
For you, who are still like a child
あぁ 試されたいなら
Ah, if you want to be tested
その愚かな手に手錠をかけて
Put handcuffs on those foolish hands
常闇の闇に囚われたまま
Trapped in the darkness of the eternal night
甘い甘いガムを噛んでいた
I was chewing sweet, sweet gum
幾つもの後悔を
Countless regrets
捧げて
Offer them up
さりげない合図に隠れた
Hidden in a casual signal
答えはすぐにわからせてあげる
I'll let you know the answer soon
微笑な嘘にまみれた
Covered in subtle lies
拒んだままに受け止めてあげる
I'll accept you as you refuse
ほら悲鳴を聞かせて
Come on, let me hear the screams
さぁ 指を鳴らしたら
Now, once you've snapped your fingers
この子猫のような私のために
For me, who am like this kitten
あら 喉が渇いたわ
Oh, I'm thirsty
薄紅の口に指を散らして
Scattering fingers on light crimson lips
狭い檻に閉じ込めたまま
While locked in a narrow cage
首輪に繋がれたいのだ
I want to be tied to a collar
くだらないルールじゃ奪えない
Can't be taken by trivial rules
自由はすでにこの手の中にある
Freedom is already in these hands
愛情では計れない
Can't be measured with affection
弱ったままに選ばせてあげる
I'll let you choose while you're weak
ほら心を開いて
Come on, open your heart
わからないふりをして
Pretending not to know
寝惚けてるの？
Are you half-asleep?
もっと熱い暗闇を見せて
Show me a hotter darkness
ねぇ
Hey
さりげない合図に隠れた
Hidden in a casual signal
答えはすぐにわからせてあげる
I'll let you know the answer soon
微笑な嘘にまみれた
Covered in subtle lies
拒んだままに受け止めてあげる
I'll accept you as you refuse
常闇の闇に刻むこの名を
Carving this name into the eternal darkness
わからせてあげる
I'll make you understand
ほら悲鳴を聞かせてよ
Come on, let me hear the screams
夢見ないで
Don't dream
ご覧になって
Look at me,
確かめて
and make sure.
風に吹かれて
Blown by the wind,
誰も気づかぬよう
so that no one notices,
区別がつかない
I can't tell the difference in
モノクロの世界
this monochrome world.
色を足しても
Even if I add color,
何も見えなくて
I can't see anything.
まるで私は
It's as if I
息を止めていた
had stopped breathing.
もういいよ
That's enough.
遠くても叶えたい
Even if it's far, I want to make it come true.
私は
I am...
越えぬ世界 想いも
A world I cannot cross, the feelings too.
抱きしめていたのに
Even though I was holding them tight,
夢のキャンバスに
on the canvas of dreams,
生き続ける意味は
the meaning of continuing to live,
この胸に
within this heart,
輝いている Story
is a shining story.
明かり灯りに
To light the light,
意味などないけれど
it doesn't have any meaning, but
拾い集めた
I gathered up
欠片 失うの？
the pieces. Will I lose them?
そして夜は その冷たさを
And the night, its coldness,
溶かして手を伸ばした
it melted away as I reached out my hand.
もういいよ
That's enough.
遠くても届けたい
Even if it's far, I want to reach it.
私は受け止めていく
I will keep accepting it.
涙も
Even the tears,
抱きしめていたのに
even though I was holding them tight,
夢のキャンバスに
on the canvas of dreams,
心込めるのは
putting my heart into it,
この空に
in this sky,
描き出していく Story
I'm drawing out a story.
そして夜は その冷たさを
And the night, its coldness,
溶かして手を伸ばした
it melted away as I reached out my hand.
もういいよ
That's enough.
遠くても叶えたい
Even if it's far, I want to make it come true.
私の
My...
越えぬ世界 想いも
world I cannot cross, the feelings too,
言葉で包んだ
I wrapped them in words.
夢のキャンバスに
On the canvas of dreams,
色を足していく
I'm adding colors.
この胸に
In this heart,
今輝いて
it's shining now.
強くなくてもいい
It's okay not to be strong.
壊れかけてもいい
It's okay if it starts to break.
この心は永遠に羽ばたいて
This heart will fly forever.
響くように
So it resonates,
塗り替えていく パレット
I'll keep repainting the palette.
だって僕は星だから
Because I'm a star.
Stellar Stellar
きっと君はもう気づいていた
Surely you've already noticed.
僕の心の奥で欠いた
Missing from deep in my heart.
それがこれから話す陳腐な
That's the trite monologue
モノローグさ
I'm about to tell you.
ずっと言えない言葉があった
There were words I could never say.
壊せない壁があったんだ
There was a wall I couldn't break down.
ずっとさ
Always.
ふっと香り立つ朝の匂いが
The scent of the morning that suddenly arises,
どうしようもなく憎らしくて
is so hopelessly hateful.
部屋の隅で膝を抱えて
Curled up in the corner of the room,
震えていた
I was trembling.
太陽なんていらないから
I don't need something like the sun
明けないでいて
Don't let the dawn break
その手を伸ばして
Reach out that hand
誰かに届くように
So that it reaches someone
僕だって君と同じ
I'm the same as you
特別なんかじゃないから
Because I'm not special or anything
そうさ僕は夜を歌うよ Stellar Stellar
That's right, I'll sing of the night, Stellar Stellar
ありったけの輝きで
With all the brilliance I have
今宵 音楽はずっとずっと止まらない
Tonight, the music will never, ever stop
そうさ僕がずっと　なりたかったのは
That's right, what I've always wanted to be
待ってるシンデレラじゃないさ
Isn't a Cinderella who just waits
迎えに行く王子様だ
It's the prince who goes to meet them
だって僕は星だから
Because I am a star
なんてありふれた話なんだ
What a commonplace story
理想だけ書き連ねていた
I was just writing down my ideals
ノートの隅に眠るほんのワンシーンだ
Just a single scene sleeping in the corner of my notebook
きっとあの星も泣いてるんだ
I'm sure that star is crying too
明日なんて来ないままでいて
Let tomorrow never come
その手を伸ばして
Reach out that hand
誰かに届くように
So that it reaches someone
本当に大切なものは目に
The things that are truly important
見えないみたいなんだ
Seem to be invisible to the eye
そうさ僕は夜を歌うよ Stellar Stellar
That's right, I'll sing of the night, Stellar Stellar
ありのまま 震えないで
Just as you are, don't tremble
今宵 音楽はきっときっと止まらない
Tonight, the music will surely, surely not stop
そうさ僕がずっと　なりたかったのは
That's right, what I've always wanted to be
あえかなヒロインじゃないさ
Isn't a faint heroine
救いに行くヒーローだ
It's the hero who goes to save
夢見がちな おとぎ話
A dreamy fairy tale
おとぎ話
Fairy tale
そうさ僕は夜を歌うよ Stellar Stellar
That's right, I'll sing of the night, Stellar Stellar
ありったけの輝きで
With all the brilliance I have
今宵 音楽はずっとずっと止まらない
Tonight, the music will never, ever stop
そうさ僕は愛を歌うよ Stellar Stellar
That's right, I'll sing of love, Stellar Stellar
世界宇宙の真ん中で
In the middle of the world and the universe
今宵 音楽はきっときっと止まらない
Tonight, the music will surely, surely not stop
そうさ僕がずっと　なりたかったのは
That's right, what I've always wanted to be
待ってるシンデレラじゃないさ
Isn't a Cinderella who just waits
迎えに行く王子様だ
It's the prince who goes to meet them
だって僕は星だから
Because I am a star
そうだ 僕は星だった
That's right, I was a star
Stellar Stellar
はーい、ではどうでしたでしょうか？ゲストコーナーでした！
Hi! So, how was that? That was the guest corner!
はい、今回はね、あのトワのオリジナル曲、そしてゲストさんのオリジナル曲をトワと一緒に歌うという構成にしてみました。
Yes, this time, I made it a setlist where I sing my original songs and the guest's original songs together with me.
どうだったかな？ね、トワがね、あの好きな曲をすごい一緒に歌ってもいいかなって言ったら、みんな快く歌おうって言ってくれて、一緒に歌って踊ることができました。
How was it? When I asked if I could sing the songs I love together with them, everyone kindly agreed, and we were able to sing and dance together.
ま、特にね、あのインドネシア組のムナとリス、初めて一緒に歌って踊ったので、すごい嬉しかったなっていう感じです。イェーイ！
Well, especially Moona and Risu from the Indonesia branch, it was my first time singing and dancing with them, so I'm really happy about that. Yay!
すごい、いろんなね、あのワルツっぽい踊りもあれば、ちょっとかっこいい踊りとかもあって、いっぱいいっぱい練習して...
There were many different types of dances, like waltz-like ones and some cool ones, so we practiced a lot...
で、今日トワどんだけいっぱいっていうの？やばいって。
And how many "ippai" did I say today? It's crazy.
え、すごい、たくさんの量を練習しまして、
Uh, I practiced a lot,
あの、こういう形でね、きれいにすごいできて嬉しいです！
and I'm happy it turned out so beautifully like this!
イエーイ！
Yay!
ま、あの、ま、いっぱいね、この、またいっぱいって言っちゃった。今日はね、いっぱいに囚われる日なの。
Well, I said "ippai" again.
Today is a day of being obsessed with "ippai".
ごめん。
Sorry.
この、あ、喋れなくなってきた。
This, ah, I'm losing my ability to talk.
これ、意識すると喋れなーーいって！
See, when I become conscious of it, I can't talk!
まあ、後日ね、感想枠やりたいと思うので、そこで、
Well, I want to do a review stream later, so there,
多くの量を、あの、話せるようになればいいなと思います。
I hope I can talk a lot then.
イエーイ！
Yay!
では、ここからは告知枠になります。告知枠？え、告知したいと思います！
Now, from here on, it's the announcement section.
Wait, I'd like to make some announcements!
はい、いつもの通り、グッズを出しまーす！ジャジャーン！
Yes, as usual, I'm releasing goods! Ta-da!
8月8日販売開始 記念グッズ3種
On sale starting August 8th. 3 types of goods.
ボールチェーン付きアクリルジオラマスタンドと、こちらはらっち先生の描き下ろしですね。
An acrylic diorama stand with a ball chain,
illustrated by Racchi-sensei.
あとはトワ様とお揃いスウェットと、あとビビのマルチケースが今回発売されます！
And also a sweatshirt matching with Towa-sama,
and a Bibi multi-case will be on sale!
イエーイ！
Yay!
で、このスウェットなんだけど、そうだね、
And about this sweatshirt, yeah,
すごい、いつもグッズを出すときに考えているのは、
something I always think about
when I release goods is,
お外にもつけていけいけいけ... お外にもつけていける、そんなグッズを出したい！ということで、
that I want to release goods that you can wear out.
So,
こんな感じのおしゃれなスウェットになりました！
it turned out to be a stylish sweatshirt like this!
イエーイ！
Yay!
もうトワもね、実物はもう見てるんだけど、
Towa has already seen the actual product,
すごい普段着できるような服なので、みんなね、一緒に着てください！
and it's something you can wear as everyday wear,
so everyone, please wear it with me!
イエーイ！
Yay!
で、この三つ全部、あの、揃ったものを、フルセットを買っていただくと、なんと！
And if you buy the full set with all three items,
surprisingly!
ダダダダダ... じゃん！はい！
Dadadadada... Jan! Yes!
フルセット購入特典 直筆サイン＆箔押し複製メッセージ入りポストカード
Full Set Bonus: Postcard with hand-written signature
and foil-stamped message.
もう今回は、皆さん、ノー喧嘩。何も、もう早い者勝ちとかないんです。
This time, everyone, no fighting.
There's no first-come-first-served or anything.
トワがね、サインを一枚一枚、直筆で書きたいと思うので、
I'll be signing each and every one of them by hand,
ぜひぜひ、フルセット買ってくれたら嬉しいなーと思います。
so I'd be very happy if you'd buy the full set.
はい、ではこのグッズはね、配信が終わってから購入できるようになるので、
Yes, so these goods will be available for purchase
after the stream ends,
購入してくださーーい！
so please buy them!
はい、以上グッズの、グッズの詳細でした。ま、単品でもね、買えるのでね、いっぱい買ってください。
That was the details of the goods.
You can buy them individually too, so buy lots!
はい。ま、ということでね、
Yes. Well, having said that,
常闇トワのソロが少ねえんじゃねえかと思った、そこのあなた。
to those of you who thought
Tokoyami Towa's solos were a bit few.
あなた、あなた。
You, you.
トワ、この後ラスト頑張っていきたいと思うので、
I want to do my best for the last part after this,
最後まで聞いてってね、よろしく！
so please listen until the end, okay! Thanks!
はい、ではソロ、歌います！ドーン！
Alright, now I'll sing a solo! Boom!
ってなんだ？はい！
What was that? Yes!
青い惑星に生まれて
Born on a blue planet
違う道を歩いて
Walking a different path
辿り着いたこの街
I arrived at this city
光る粒が弾けた
Glowing particles burst
巡る夜にキミと出会い
Meeting you in the revolving night
いつの間にか手を繋いで
Before I knew it, we were holding hands
笑い声と弾む足で
With laughter and bouncy steps
どこまでも駆けるミッドナイト
Running anywhere in the midnight
見上げた空 星の光
Looking up at the sky, the starlight
街のネオンが混じり合って
Mixing with the city's neon lights
憂鬱な日々を忘れて
Forgetting the melancholic days
全部 捨て去って
Throwing everything away
ボクらもっと自由なはず
We should be much freer
閉ざした羽を開いたなら
If we open our closed wings
退屈な日々にさよなら
Goodbye to the boring days
夜の街を行こう さあ
Let's go through the night city, come on
ビルを抜けて
Passing through the buildings
街を追い越して
Overtaking the city
さらば青い惑星
Farewell, blue planet
なんて惚けてどこまで行こう
Going anywhere with such absent-mindedness
変わらないものなど
Things that don't change
何もないから
Because there are none
たった一つ
Only one
確かな今を刻んで
Carving out the certain present
踊る夜にキミを連れて
Taking you along on this dancing night
邪魔なものは何らもなくて
There's nothing to get in our way
歌う声と軽い足で
With singing voices and light footsteps
いつまでも駆けるミッドナイト
Running through the midnight forever
見上げた空 月の光
Looked up at the sky, the moonlight
街の幻想が惹かれあって
The illusions of the city are drawn to each other
憂鬱な日々を忘れて
Forgetting the melancholic days
苦い 暗いはもう全部捨て去って
Bitterness and darkness, throw them all away now
見上げた空 星の光
Looked up at the sky, the starlight
街のネオンが混じり合って
The city's neon lights are mixing
退屈な日々にさよなら
Goodbye to the boring days
ボクの手を取ってさあ
Take my hand, come on
最後は常闇トワオリジナル曲
The last one is a Tokoyami Towa original song
本日初披露
Performing for the first time today
新曲
New song
「ライメイ」
“Raimei”
だって、私いつまでもずっと虜
Because I'll always be captivated
君以外はもうありえない
It can't be anyone but you anymore
ちょっといつもふらふら
Always a bit unsteady
そっぽ向くの？
Are you looking away?
思わせぶり許さないからね
I won't forgive those suggestive looks
好きだよって
Saying “I love you”
かわいいねって
Saying “You're cute”
甘やかして盲信
Spoiling me, blind faith
あのね　無理だよって
You know, saying it's impossible
いけるよって
Saying we can do it
揺れたって落魄
Even if we waver, downfall
ガラスハートを振り回して
Swinging around my glass heart
骨の髄までしゃぶり尽くして
Devour me to the bone
壊れるほど惑わせて
Bewilder me until I break
you know, you know, you know
love you
手のひらで転がして
Roll me in your palm
弩級時間を駆け抜けて
Running through tremendous time
痺れる声はライメイ
The numbing voice is thunder
勝手な妄想なんだけど
It's just my own delusion
こっち向いて 君以外はもう愛せない
Look this way, I can't love anyone but you anymore
きっと気分屋なんだけど
I'm probably just moody
いつか私、ヤキモチで狂いそうだから
Because someday I might go crazy with jealousy
貢いじゃって
Spending on you
いらついちゃって
Getting annoyed
突きつけたい銃口
Wanting to point the muzzle
これはサンクコスト？
Is this a sunk cost?
ただの愛憎？
Just love-hate?
なんだっていいけど
Anything is fine though
自分ファーストで手懐けて
Tame me with yourself first
ぬくい鳥籠で飼い殺して
Keeping me in a warm birdcage
あざといくらいの笑顔で
With a smile that's almost too calculating
you know, you know, you know
その熱量で不機嫌なのに
Even though I'm grumpy with that heat
ヤバイキュートな身のこなしが
My crazy cute behavior
病を思うほど悩殺
Captivating to the point of sickness
気分次第でもっと頂戴
Give me more depending on your mood
幻だって That's all right
Even if it's a phantom, that's all right
あぁ、このまま地獄へと
Ah, just like this, to hell
さあ生存 together
Now, survive together
Low Low Low Low Low...
La La La La La...
ガラスハートを振り回して
Swinging around my glass heart
歌った今までが全部
Everything I've sung up until now
あなた自身の心だって
Is your own heart
Do you know? you know? you know?
love you
手のひらで転がした
I rolled you in my palm
私だけを愛していて
Keep on loving only me
蠱惑的なほど痺れる恋はライメイ？
Is a love so numbing it's enchanting, thunder?
蠱惑的なほど痺れる恋はライメイ
A love so numbing it's enchanting is thunder
サムネイル制作
IKKI
Thumbnail Production
オープニング
Rely
RIDE名
にーえぬ
Opening
Rely
RIDEna
Nienu
エンディング
Rely
RIDE名
Ending
Rely
RIDEna
撮影、企画補佐: カバー株式会社
Filming, Planning Assistance: Cover Corp.
SPECIAL THANKS
谷間晄
Akira Tanima
MIX
BIRTHDAY FESTIVAL 2022
TOKOYAMI TOWA
常闇トワ生誕祭
MIX
BIRTHDAY FESTIVAL 2022
TOKOYAMI TOWA
Tokoyami Towa Birthday Festival